Environmental Advocates of New York; Records apap104
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Environmental Advocates of New York Website, 2001 April 28 - 2017 June 1; 10; 260 captures
  - ENVIRONMENTAL ADVOCATES OF NEW YORK, 2013 April 14
  - ENVIRONMENTAL ADVOCATES OF NEW YORK, 2013 April 24
  - ENVIRONMENTAL ADVOCATES OF NEW YORK, 2013 May 29
  - ENVIRONMENTAL ADVOCATES OF NEW YORK, 2013 May 31
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2013 July 28
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2013 July 30
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2013 August 16
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2013 October 18
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2013 November 14
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2013 November 20
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2013 November 20
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2013 November 28
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2013 December 11
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2013 December 11
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2014 February 8
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2014 February 22
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2014 March 20
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2014 March 27
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2014 May 8
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2014 May 10
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2014 May 21
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2014 June 26
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2014 September 11
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2014 September 30
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2014 October 12
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2014 October 15
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2014 November 5
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2014 December 8
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2014 December 19
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2015 January 9
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2015 January 29
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2015 February 8
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2015 March 10
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2015 March 11
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2015 March 29
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2015 May 12
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2015 May 20
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2015 June 24
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2015 June 27
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2015 July 27
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2015 September 1
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2015 September 5
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2015 September 11
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2015 October 4
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2015 November 4
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2015 November 21
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 January 14
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 January 18
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 January 22
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 February 13
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 March 4
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 March 11
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 March 15
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 March 19
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 April 4
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 May 6
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 May 31
    crawl: 215651
    Crawl Rules
    Crawl Times
    start_date: 2016-05-31T19:51:06Z
    original_start_date: 2016-05-31T19:51:06Z
    last_resumption: None
    processing_end_date: 2016-06-03T22:14:58Z
    end_date: 2016-06-03T20:04:43Z
    elapsed_ms: 260012500
    Crawl Types
    type: NONE
    recurrence_type: NONE
    pdfs_only: False
    test: False
    Crawl Limits
    time_limit: 259200
    document_limit: None
    byte_limit: None
    crawl_stop_requested: None
    Crawl Results
    status: FINISHED_TIME_LIMIT
    discovered_count: 1993850
    novel_count: 711861
    duplicate_count: 12531
    resumption_count: 0
    queued_count: 1269458
    downloaded_count: 724392
    download_failures: 21
    warc_revisit_count: 12345
    warc_url_count: 724374
    total_data_in_kbs: 57035352
    duplicate_bytes: 2587600674
    warc_compressed_bytes: 2458477182
    Crawl Technical Details
    doc_rate: 2.79
    kb_rate: 219.0
  - WARC file for Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 May 31
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Researchers interested in data analysis with web archives may request a WARC file. WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in advanced research with web archives.
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 May 31
  - WARC file for Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 May 31
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 June 8
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 June 29
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 July 10
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 July 31
    crawl: 228120
    start_date: 2016-07-31T14:49:32Z
    original_start_date: 2016-07-31T14:49:32Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-08-03T15:18:53Z
    end_date: 2016-08-03T14:51:29Z
    elapsed_ms: 259288678
    type: TEST_SAVED
    test: True
    discovered_count: 94584
    novel_count: 27450
    duplicate_count: 2792
    queued_count: 64342
    downloaded_count: 30242
    download_failures: 12
    warc_revisit_count: 2757
    warc_url_count: 30229
    total_data_in_kbs: 1588506
    duplicate_bytes: 338611721
    warc_compressed_bytes: 451373731
    doc_rate: 0.12
    kb_rate: 6.0
  - WARC file for Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 July 31
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 July 31
  - WARC file for Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 July 31
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 August 3
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 August 12
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 August 25
    crawl: 232505
    Limit host twitter.com to 500 documents
    start_date: 2016-08-25T19:13:00Z
    original_start_date: 2016-08-25T19:13:00Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-08-30T19:41:37Z
    end_date: 2016-08-30T19:17:54Z
    elapsed_ms: 432246025
    time_limit: 432000
    discovered_count: 123374
    novel_count: 39715
    duplicate_count: 2217
    queued_count: 81442
    downloaded_count: 41932
    download_failures: 4
    warc_revisit_count: 2190
    warc_url_count: 41860
    total_data_in_kbs: 1972395
    duplicate_bytes: 308602245
    warc_compressed_bytes: 583002982
    doc_rate: 0.1
    kb_rate: 4.0
  - WARC file for Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 August 25
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 August 25
  - WARC file for Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 August 25
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 September 14
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 September 17
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 October 15
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 October 16
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2016 November 16
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2017 February 3
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2017 February 5
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2017 March 13
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2017 March 16
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2017 May 19
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2017 June 1
    crawl: 304464
    Limit host fbcdn.net to 500 documents
    Limit host facebook.com to 500 documents
    Limit host twimg.com to 500 documents
    start_date: 2017-06-01T20:49:39Z
    original_start_date: 2017-06-01T20:49:39Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-06-04T23:51:23Z
    end_date: 2017-06-04T20:50:40Z
    elapsed_ms: 259236635
    type: MONTHLY
    recurrence_type: MONTHLY
    discovered_count: 83184
    novel_count: 25582
    duplicate_count: 1793
    queued_count: 55809
    downloaded_count: 27375
    warc_revisit_count: 1786
    warc_url_count: 27366
    total_data_in_kbs: 1572427
    duplicate_bytes: 312923523
    warc_compressed_bytes: 557584792
    doc_rate: 0.11
  - WARC file for Environmental Advocates of New York, 2017 June 1